Guide to the Yoshio Kishi Papers MSS.351
Fales Library and Special Collections
Yoshio Kishi Papers
1892-2011
1950-2005
Fales Library and Special Collections
Kishi, Yoshio, 1932-2012
MSS.351
5.69 Linear Feet in 13 manuscript boxes
Yoshio Kishi was an award-winning New York City based film and sound editor working on notable films such Martin Scorcese's Raging Bull (1980) and Wayne Wang's Dim Sum: A Little Bit of Heart (1985). When not working on films, Kishi avidly collected materials that trace depictions of Asian Americans in U.S. intellectual and popular culture, as well as materials produced by Asian American activists to counter stereotypical imagery of Asian peoples. Kishi eventually amassed over 10,000 items, allowing him to trace Asian and Asian American depictions throughout two centuries of American history. In addition to his collection of Asian Americana, Kishi dedicated time to tracing his own family lineage, documenting his family through correspondence, photographs, and his own personal research notes. The Yoshio Kishi Papers roughly span from 1892 to 2011, with the bulk of the materials dating between the 1950s to the mid-2000s. This collection contains correspondence, photographs, personal notes, photocopied articles, filmography lists, pamphlets and interview videos with Kishi that discuss his career as an artist, his family, and his collections of Asian American materials.
Biographical Note
Yoshio Kishi (1932- 2012) was an award-winning professional New York City based film and sound editor. Kishi was born in 1932 to Eikichi and Haru Kishi, both of whom immigrated from Japan to the United States. Kishi had four siblings: Hajime, Fumi, Mitsuo, and Isomi. He was educated at the Bronx High School of Sciences, the City College of New York, Herzliah Hebrew Teachers Institute, the Fashion Institute of Technology, and the New School for Social Research. Kishi briefly taught at New York's Film Institute and served as a juror for directing and editing at the Emmy Awards.
Kishi worked as an editor on Martin Scorcese's Raging Bull (1980), Alan Parker's Fame (1980), as well as Wayne Wang's Dim Sum: A Little Bit of Heart (1985). Kishi also worked as a sound editor on Jerry Schatzberg's Panic in Needle Park (1971) and, in addition to serving as the editor, Kishi also directed Lombardi (1968).
For four decades, Kishi avidly collected materials that traced depictions of Asian Americans in U.S. intellectual and popular culture, as well as materials produced by Asian American activists to counter stereotypical imagery of Asian peoples. His compulsion for collecting Asian Americana began in the mid-1960s when, reflecting upon his own identity as a second-generation Japanese American, Kishi began to regret not knowing more about his ethnic heritage. Kishi grew up in a largely Irish and Italian tenement neighborhood and during World War II, to avoid being labeled enemy aliens, his parents stopped speaking Japanese and joined a local Lutheran Church. In an effort to reclaim his ethnic heritage, Kishi, with the help of Los Angeles-based veteran actress and friend, Irene Yah Ling Sun, began to scour flea markets to purchase any materials relating to Asian Americana. Kishi eventually amassed over 10,000 items showcasing the demonization, as well as activism efforts of Asian Americans. Kishi's vast collection allowed him to trace Asian and Asian American depictions throughout two centuries of American history.
In his later life, Yoshio Kishi developed a relationship with New York University's Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute and in 2003, he sold his collection of Asian Americana to New York University, on behalf of the A/P/A Institute. Kishi's collection, later titled the "Yoshio Kishi and Irene Yah-Ling Sun Collection" (MSS.292), was purchased with the intention of making its contents publicly available for research by students, scholars, and any other interested parties. Although Kishi parted with most of his Asian Americana collection, he did retain some materials for personal use, which laid the groundwork for the Yoshio Kishi Papers (MSS.351).
Yoshio Kishi died in 2012.
Arrangement
This collection has been arranged into series by topic:
I. Works II. Collection of Asian American Materials III. Personal Materials
Within each series, the materials have been arranged alphabetically.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Related Materials
For more information about Yoshio Kishi's collection of Asian American materials, see the the Yoshio Kishi and Irene Yah-Ling Sun Collection (MSS.292).
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Dylan Yeats acquired the collection from Yoshio Kishi's nursing home after Kishi's death. Yeats later donated the collection to Fales Library at New York University
Scope and Contents
The Yoshio Kishi Papers roughly span from 1892 to 2011, with the bulk of the materials dating between the 1950s to the mid-2000s. The collection documents various aspects of Kishi's professional and private life, as well as his contributions as a collector of Asian American materials.
The collection contains correspondence between Kishi and his family members, friends, colleagues, as well as other collectors of Asian American ephemera. There are several volumes of Kishi's journals that contain insights into his daily life, as well as drafts of project ideas, poems, and other creative writings.
As a second generation Japanese American, Kishi was especially concerned with stereotypical Asian American imagery in the United States, and to this effect, the collection contains vast quantities of research materials such as photocopies of articles and book chapters that examine racist portrayals of Asian peoples in film, photocopies of old Hollywood movie posters such as the Humphrey Bogart film Tokyo Joe (1949), as well as newspaper clippings related to famous Asian celebrities such as Anna May Wong and Michelle Wei. It should be noted the collection, particularly in Series II, does contain material that may be deemed offensive and/or racist.
The Yoshio Kishi Papers also includes documents relating to the Yoshio Kishi and Irene Yah-Ling Sun Collection (MSS.292), which was purchased from Yoshio Kishi in 2003 by New York University's Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) Institute. These documents include drafts of the legal agreements between Kishi and New York University, inventories of the Kishi/Sun Collection, brochures promoting the Kishi/Sun collection, and photographs from the "Archivist of the Yellow Peril" exhibition host by the A/P/A Institute in 2005. The "Archivist of the Yellow Peril" exhibition provided glimpses of the Kishi/Sun Collection's 8000+ rare artifacts.
The Yoshio Kishi Papers contains photographs and photo negatives whose subject matters range from general everyday life, Kishi's family, and Asian American stereotypes. The collection also contains one audioreel entitled "Mama" and two video interviews with Yoshio Kishi that have been recorded on VHS tapes.
Brochures.; Clippings (information artifacts); Photographs.; Printed ephemera.; Videocassettes.; Audiocassettes.; Screenplays; Diaries; Letters.; Manhattan (New York, N.Y.); Japan.; Pacific Islanders; Chinese Americans.; Japanese American artists.; Japanese American literature.; Stereotypes (Social psychology) in mass media -- United States.; Collectors and collecting.; Racism.; Certificates.; Kishi, Yoshio, 1932-2012; Kishi, Haru; Wong, Anna May, 1905-1961
- Series I: Works, 1955-2010
  Scope and Contents
  Series I largely focuses upon Yoshio Kishi's work as a film professional. The series contains correspondence between Kishi and various productions companies such as Pathe Films and NFL Films, discssuing past and future collaborations, as well as copies of Kishi's resumes and video editing certificate, highlighting his career achievements. Materials related to Kishi's major film projects, Dim Sum: A Little Bit of Heart and Lombardi can be found within this series. Additionally, drafts, outlines, and proposals for Kishi's other film projects such as Vietnam Song, Empress of China, and Soulmate (The Black Hole) can also be found within this series.
  Series I also contains samples of Kishi's poetry and short stories, which are housed within his diaries and notes. This series also contains materials related to Kishi's growing advocacy of Asian American culture, a driving force behind Kishi's passion for collection Asian Americana. Kishi's participation in pro-Asian and pro-Asian American organizations are reflected in folders such as "Asian Americans for Action" (Box 1, Folder 3), the "Ethnic Heritage Studies Program Act" (Box 1, Folder 18) and "Yellow Peril" (Box 3, Folder 15).
  - Amerasia Resources, Inc., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Asian-American Collections, 1971-2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Asian Americans for Action, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Asian American Repository, Vol 1 Issue 1, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - China Unearthed - Budget, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chinatown History Museum, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence -- Andrew Watt, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence -- Isomi Handrych, 2002-2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence -- Meri von Sternberg, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence -- Pathe Pictures, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence -- Steve Sabol (NFL Films), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CUNY Department of Asian Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dim Sum, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Eikichi and Haru Kishi Collection of Asian Americana, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Employee Termination Letter (MPO Productions), 1955 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Empress of China, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - Ethnic Heritage Studies Program Act, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Final Mix: Revised, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "The Goddess Maker", 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Google Books Screenshots, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Great Collaboration, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ideas, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - In Quest of Chinatown, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Joan of Arc Junior High School Reunions, 1995-2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Josef von Sternberg, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - KHAN! Draft Script, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lombardi, 1968-2010 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - MD-USN, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Media Works (FIVF-CETA), 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - "Murrow", 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - National Endowment for the Arts General Programs, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Clipping - New York Times, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Poetry, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 15, Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Proposals, 1961-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Resumes, 1974-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - "Scrutable Contexts: Asian Threads in the American Fabric", 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sensual Delights: An Asian American Erotic Feast, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Soulmate (The Black Hole), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Trust, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Video Editing Certificate, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Vietnam - Story Ideas, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Vietnam Song, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Window, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Winter Blossom, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Yellow Peril", 2005-2008 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Series II: Collection of Asian American Materials, 1892-2011
  Series II focuses upon Yoshio Kishi's passion for collecting Asian Americana and his acquisition of research materials relating to stereotypical portrayals of Asian peoples and culture throughout history, as well as within American popular culture. The correspondence found within this series either contains discussion between Kishi and other collectors of Asian materials focusing upon the sale and purchase of Asian materials or Kishi's requests for research materials.
  The photocopies found within Series II are research materials comprising of excerpts from scholarly monographs and journal articles, copies of Hollywood movie posters, copies of pulp magazine covers, and newspaper clipping about Asian celebrities like Anna May Wong and Michelle Wei. Other printed materials such as inventories, eBay printouts, catalogs, and price lists relate to the acquisition of Asian Americana materials. The photographs in this series focus upon either historic depictions or stereotypical depcitions of Asian peoples and culture.
  This series also includes a VHS tape containing an interview with Yoshio Koshio conducted by Jack Tchen of NYU's A/P/A Institute.
  It should be noted that this series contains some materials that may be deemed offensive and/or racist.
  - Acrobats, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Advertisement for Movie Posters, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Advertisements from NYU Asian/Pacific/American Institute, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Anna May Wong, 1931, 1976-2004 (Box 4, Folder 4, Box Shared Fales 042, Folder 1)
  - Asian Americana (Kishi Sun Collection), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Asian/American Center at Queens College Activities, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Asian American Studies Program at Cornell University Newsletter, Vol. 3, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Asian American Studies Resources, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Asian Americans Through the Lens, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 美學概論 (Bigaku Gairon or Aesthetic Theory), undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Books - Prices, 1994, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Books for Sale, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Chiang-Chiang Dance Company, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - "The 'Chinese Question' and American Labor Historians", 2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Chou Tun-i (1017-1073) of the Sung Dynasty, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Circuses, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Copies of Advertisements Related to Asian Portrayals, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Copies of Books/Articles about Asian Stereotypes, 1943-1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence -- Aaron, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence -- Arnold's Used Books, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence -- Asian/Pacific/American Institute NYU, Re: Kishi-Sun Collection, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 21, Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence -- Bowers and Merena Galleries, Inc., 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- David Chow, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- DJ Ernst, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence -- Elaine Mae Woo, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence -- Hollywood Studio Magazine, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence -- Mrs. Jo Van Dorp, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence -- Rebekah Montgomery, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence -- Tome Moroccan, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence -- University of Arizona, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence -- University of Hawaii, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "Doubleness: American Images of Japanese Men in Silent Spy Films", 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Draft of Agreement of Sale for Yoshio Kishi Collection to NYU, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - "Early Film Magazines - An Overview", undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - eBay Printouts - Asian Collector Materials, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - eBay Printouts - Japan Postcards, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Elbae-Spring Binders Advertisement, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Film List, 1929-1939 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Film Poster Dealers and Guidelines for Collecting Movie Posters, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Gluck, E.W., "An Ecological Study of the Japanese in New York City", undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - "Hojo-ki (A Description of My Hut)", 1925 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - The Japan Weekly Mail, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - "Japanese Americans" Notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Japanese in New York, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - "Last Will & Testament" (Asian American Legal Defense & Education Fund Pamphlet), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Magazines Checked, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Magazine Clippings - Variety, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Momo Taro (Romaji), 1998, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Museum of Modern Art Department of Film American Film Posters inventory, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - New York City Chinatown brochure, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - "New York's Issei and Coney Island", 1964 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - New York Times article about the Kishi Collection, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Newspaper Clipping -- "A Book on Jews Stirs Japanese", undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Newspaper Clippings -- Michelle Wei, 2005 (Box Shared Fales 043, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings -- Political Cartoons, 1990-1997 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Newspaper Clipping -- Variety, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Notes & Bibliographic Citations, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Notebook, 1982, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - NYU Asian/Pacific/American Institute Calendar of Events, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Orientalism, 2009-2011 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Peachboy Nights, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Photocopies -- Film Books, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Photocopies -- "Notable Films of the Week", 1909 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Photocopies -- Political Cartoons, 1975-1991 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Photographs -- "Archivist of the Yellow Peril" exhibit, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Photograph -- Chinese Actor, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Photographs -- Everyday Life of Chinese Peoples, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Photographs -- Japanese Concentration Camps Exhibit, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Photographs -- Yoshio Kishi's Book Collection, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Photographs and Negatives Depicting Asian Peoples and Movie Stills, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Photo Negatives -- "Plain Language from Truthful James", undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - The Play Pictorial, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - "The Politics of Portraiture", 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Requests for Research Materials, 1982-1992 (Box 6, Folder 16-21)
  - Research Materials, 1909-2004 (Box 6, Folder 22-23)
  - Research Materials about Asian Peoples, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Research Notes, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
  - Sakura Matsuri, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sawada, Mitzi - The Japanese Immigrant in New York City, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "Scrutable Images: Asians and Asian Americans in Mass Culture", 1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Selected List of Films, 1908-1924 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sheet Music, 1986-2000 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Shiel, M.P., 1898, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Henry D. II, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - A Social Study of the Japanese Population in the Greater New York Area, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Son of Native register, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Tom Matsuda, 1999-2007 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Trade Cards, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Tsiang, H.T., 1899-1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - VHS Tape -- Yoshio Kishi Interview with Jack Tchen, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - The Vocational Opportunities of the Second Generation Japanese in Greater New York and their Bearings on Religious Education, 1935-1936 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Watanna, Ono, 1900-1929 (Box Shared Fales 042, Folder 2)
  - Weglyn, Michi (Years of Infamy), 1976-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "Yellow Face", 2005 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Yellow Peril, 1983-1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Series III: Personal Materials, 1922-2009
  Series III focuses upon Yoshio Kishi's private life, his family, and personal interests. A large focus of Series III is Kishi's desire to learn more about his own family history. This can be seen through his vast collection of family photographs, detailed family trees, individual files about family members, and discussions with his family regarding their Japanese origins. Kishi's mother, Haru, features heavily within this series through letters, photographs, legals documents (social security card, passports), and medical documents.
  In addition to his family, this series contains insights into Yoshio Kishi's private life through several journals, financial statements, school transcripts, travel documents, newspaper articles, photographs, and legal paperwork.
  The correspondence housed within this series is mainly between Kishi and his family, although there are some letters from friends and Kishi's personal physician. The photographs and photograph negatives found within this series depict Kishi's family, apartment, personal acquaintances, as well as moments from everyday life.
  Series III also contains an audioreel entitled "Mama" and a VHS tape interview with Yoshio Kishi.
  - Asahi Video Library - Interview: "Experiences of the Japanese American Issei in NY", 1998 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Audio Reel -- "Mama", undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Autobiographical Notes, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Beneficiary Document - Motion Picture Editor's Union, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Birthday Card, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Board of Education of the City of New York Certificate, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Bronx High School of Science, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "The Care & Feeding of E, S, K", 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Certificate of Acceptability, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Certificate of Appreciation for Haru Kishi, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Christmas Card from Haru Kishi, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - City College of New York Transcript, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1922, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 16-21, Box 12, Folder 10-12)
  - Correspondence -- Dr. Condon, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence -- Encampment for Citizenship, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence -- Eva Haberman to Isomi Handrych, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence -- Family, 1963-2003 (Box 8, Folder 25-26)
  - Correspondence -- Film Quarterly, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence -- Fumi Yasutake, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence -- Isomi Handrych, 1970, 1990-2002 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence -- Major G.J. Mitchell, Jr., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence -- Manfred, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence -- Michael Blackwood, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence -- Mits Kishi, 1987, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence -- Mr. Kawano Michikazu, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence -- Mrs. A. Kondo, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence -- Naojiro Kobashima, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence -- New York Buddhist Church, undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence -- Stechert-Hafner, Inc., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence -- Yomiuri Shinbun, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence -- Yoshio Kishi, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Yoshio Kishi to Family, 1963, 1985, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and Documents related to Haru Kishi, 1986-1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Cypress Hill Cemetery Payment Record Book, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Dawn Barnard, 1985-1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Dawn Lawson, 1999, 2007, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Diary Entry, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Duplicate Photographs and Documents, undated (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
  - Family Accident Protector Application, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Family E-mails about Yoshio Kishi, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Family Financial Log, 1982-1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Family Tree, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Financial Materials, 1961-1993 (Box 9, Folder 14-16, Box 12, Folder 10, 12)
  - Fumiko no kawaii tegami (letter), undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Inventories, Lists, Receipts, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Japan Air Lines Passenger Tickets and Baggage Check Books, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Journal, 1968-2007 (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
  - Journal Entries, 1949-1992 (Box 10, Folder 5-8, Box 12, Folder 11-12)
  - Journal Entries and Personal Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
  - Journal Entries, Correspondence, Notes, and Photographs, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Kelly Robinson/Desiree Lea Brimberry, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Kishi, Eikichi - Biographical Sketch, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Kishi, Haru, 1922-2002 (Box 11, Folder 1, 16, Box 8, Folder 29-31, Box 9, Folder 18-22, Box 12, Folder 1-2)